Viraj Tank

+91 9737 933039 · virajtank98@gmail.com · Portfolio · Github · LinkedIn

SOFTWARE ENGINEER (MOBILE APPLICATION DEVELOPER)

Enthusiastic Learner! always focused on maximizing my every learning experience, possessing a strong willingness to learn about entrepreneurship/businesses and I might know the value of the intangible asset of all time which is TIME!

EXPERTISE AND STRENGTHS

Flutter Kotlin / JAVA Node.js (Basics)

SwiftUI (Basics) Firebase Project Management Tools

Google APIs / Social Integration Github / Postman / Figma Work Under Pressure / Multitasking

Teamwork Blog Writing Attention to Detail

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Virva Infotech March 2023 - Present

Flutter/Native Android Developer

- Building crossplatform app from scratch which allows users to record and store all your important moments, memories and trips, No matter when they happened!
- Writing Tech Blogs

Freelancer

Flutter/Native Android Developer

- Building Student Transportation app, There are 2 different apps for both Parents and Drivers (Tech stack: Flutter / Firebase / Realtime Location Tracking / Firebase Storage)
- Building Pet Social media / community app (Tech stack: Flutter)
- Built crossplatform app for one solution for fraud-detection, identity proofing, compliance adherence, risk management and innovations in data management (Tech stack: Flutter)

Version Systems Aug 2022 - Feb 2023

Flutter/Native Android Developer

- Worked with Google In-app subscriptions & Apple In-App Purchase also Google AdMob in flutter
- · Convert offline support for whole flutter app using sqflite to provide users seamless experience
- Managed Apple store & Play Store Distribution

TilesWale / Light Link Solutions

June 2021 - July 2022

Native Android Developer (Kotlin / JAVA)

- Learned and Implemented Kotlin Jetpack components in the product (Hilt DI, Jetpack Components, etc.)
- Managed Play store distribution & Vitals
- · Collaboration with the Product Manager & Business Analyst to ensure quality in all phases of development.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Engineering

Atmiya Institute of Technology & Science 2018-2021